Guide to the Daryl B. Lund papers, 1995-2000.
Lund, Daryl B. papers, 1995-2000
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Daryl B. Lund papers, 1995-2000.
21-1-3463
Lund, Daryl B.
6 cubic ft.
Reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection contains departmental reports, budget reports committee reports, correspondence and subject files.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Dr. Lund served as Dean of the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection contains departmental reports, budget reports committee reports, correspondence and subject files.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Daryl B. Lund.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Administration.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- I. Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 1-15)
  - Bailey Hort/Plant Bio Merger Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Biochemistry, Molecular and Cell Biology Review Objectives, Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bioethics - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Biology Restructuring - Organizational Structure, Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Biology Restructuring - Undergraduate Biology (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Biological Division - Accounting Plan (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Biological Science - Reorganization (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Biological Sciences Task Force (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bio-Reorganization - Lead Dean Concept (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Merging Bailey Hort and Plant Biology (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - BMCB/G & D Merger (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - DUB Plan - Office of Undergraduate Biology (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - OUB (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - OUB (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CALS Vision for Community & Economic Development (Box 1, Folder 15)
- II. Biological Sciences Task Force (Box 1, Folder 16-20)
  - Environmental Sciences Discussion (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Environmental Sciences Discussion (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Microbiology Reorganization (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Physiology (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Food Quality Protection Act (FQPA) (Box 1, Folder 20)
- III. Genomics Initiative, Reports (Box 1, 2, Folder 21-31, 1-2)
  - Genomics (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Genomics - Crops '99 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Genomics Initiative (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Genomics Initiative (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Genomics Initiative (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Genomics Initiative - Budget (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Genomics Initiative - Emerson Bldg (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Genomics - Emerson Center Project (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - New York State Genomics Position (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Genomics - Terry Magnuson (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Genomics Thrusts (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Social Dimensions of Genomics (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Genomics - USDA (Box 2, Folder 2)
- IV. Cornell Administration - Reports, Correspondence (Box 2, 3, Folder 3-34, 1-27)
  - Academic Programs and Campus Affairs - David Yeh (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Academic Programs Appendix 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Administration, Cornell University (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Ag. Exp. Station Appendix 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Geneva Ag Exp. Station Appendix 3 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Coop. Ext. CALS Appendix 4 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Associate Provost for Admissions (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - BOA - Biotechnology Committee (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees/ Cornell University Council (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bylaws - Cornell University (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bylaws - Cornell University (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - CALS Leadership Team, Faculty Prod. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - CALS Report to CU Board of Trustees, March 1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Charter, Cornell University (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cornell/SUNY Relationship (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cornell/SUNY Relationship (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Cornell University and Ithaca (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Dean of Faculty (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Dean of Students (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Director of Special Projects, Office of the President and the Provosts (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Environmental Health and Safety (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Genomics - Legislature Advocacy (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Government Affairs (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Governmental Affairs (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Government Affairs (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Government Affairs (old) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Human Relations AVP (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Libraries, Cornell University annual report, 1998-1999, etc. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Office of Government Affairs, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - President Rawlings (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Priorities for CALS (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Provosts Committee on Economics (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Don Randel, Provost (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Don Randel- "The Pressures on Higher Education Today" (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Report to the Provost, August 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Report to the Provost, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Report to the Provost, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Report to the Provost, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Reports to the Provost, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Residential Communitites Committee Report (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Fred Rogers, SVP and CFO (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Statutory College Affairs (Fawcett) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Trustees, Board of Cornell University (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Tuition, 2000/2001 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate Business Management (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - University Admissions (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - University Council- Administrative Board (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - University Council- Administrative Board (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - University Council (lawyers) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - University Human Rersources (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - University Relations- Dullea (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - University Relations (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - University Relations (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - University Relations- Congressional Visits (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Vice President for Academic Programs, Planning, Budgeting (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Vice President for Academic Programs, Planning, Budgeting (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Vice Provosts (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Vice Provost for Diversity and Faculty Development (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - A Vision for NYS Agriculture (Box 3, Folder 27)
- V. Budget- State and Federal (Box 3, 4, Folder 28-32, 1-11)
  - Budget College (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Charlie's Sideways Chart (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Budget- New York State (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - State Budget (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - State Budget (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - SUNY Budget (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - State Budget Initiatives, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - State Budget Potential Shortfall (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - State SUNY FY '00 Budget (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - SUNY Budget FY'01 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - SUNY Merit-based Performance Funding (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Proposed New SUNY Resource Allocation Model (RAM) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - SUNY Program Requests, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Budget- Federal (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Federal Budget, 1999(FY) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Federal Budget, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- VI. Initiatives (Box 4, Folder 12-20)
  - Faculty Productivity Indicators- Confidential (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Agriculture Initiative (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Agriculture Initiative (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Agricultural Systems Initiative (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Agricultural Systems Initiative (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Plant and Animal Initiative (PAI) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Plant and Animal Science Initiative (PASI) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Plant and Animal Systems Initiative (PASI) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Plant and Animal Systems Initiative (PASI) Continued (Box 4, Folder 20)
- VII. President's Academic Cabinet (PAC) (Box 4, 5, 6, Folder 21-30, 1-126, 1-46)
  - Agendas and Notes (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Academic Cabinet- General (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Architecture, Art, & Planning (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - PAC- China Initiative (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - PAC- President's Academic Cabinet Computing and Information Science (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - PAC- Center for the Environment (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - PAC- Center for the Environment (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - PAC- Development (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - PAC- Cornell (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - PAC- Geology (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - PAC- Geology (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Academic Cabinet- Graduate Enrollment (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - PAC- Latino Studies Program (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - PAC- Middle States Accredidation (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Program Reviews (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Academic Cabinet- Psychology (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - PAC- Public Affairs (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Academic Cabinet- Social Sciences (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Core Competencies in the Northeast Region (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Social Science Review (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Agribusiness Management & Agricultural Marketing (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Agricultural Policy & Trade (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Agriculture, Extension & Adult Education (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Agroforestry (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - American Indian Program (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Animal Behavior/Behavioral Ecology (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Animal Breeding & Genetics (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Animal Management Systems (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Animal Nutrition (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Animal Physiology (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Applied Ecology (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Aquaculture (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Atmospheric Science (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Basic Biochemical Mechanisms (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Basic Biomolecular Structure and Biophysics (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Behavioral Neurobiology (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Biogeochemistry & Environmental Changes (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Biology of Plant Diseases (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Biological and Behavioral Aspects of Human Nutrition (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Biological Engineering (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Biological Control (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Biometry (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Cell Biology (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Cellular Physiology (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Chemical Ecology (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Community Analysis (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Community Development & Economic Growth (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Community Nutrition (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Conservation Biology (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Conservation & Sustainable Development (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Controlled Environment Agriculture (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Dairy Systems (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Developmental Genetics (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Economic Biology (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Ecosystem Biology (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Educational Psychology (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Environment and Society (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Environmental & Biochemical Toxicology (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Environmental Engineering (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Environmental Microbiology (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Environmental & Resource Economics (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Evolutionary Biology (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Family and Life Course (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Farming ALternatives (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Farm Management and Finance (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Fish and Wildlife Biology Management (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Food & Fiber Production Engineering (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Food Quality (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Food Safety Enhancement (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Food Systems for Improved Health (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Forage-Livestock Systems (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Human Communication Systems & Processes (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Human-Impacted Ecological Change (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Information Systems & Technology (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Insect Biology (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Integrated Field Crop, Soil, & Pest Management (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Forest Biology and Management (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Fruit Systems (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Fruit Integrated Pest Management (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Fungal Biology (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - General Biology Teaching (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Gender Relations and Development (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Global Climate Change (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Integrated Pest Management-Vegetable Crops (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Integrated Resource Management (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Integrated Turfgrass & Environmental Management (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - International Animal Agriculture (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - International Economic Development & Trade (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - International Nutrition (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Invertebrate Biology (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Landscape Architecture (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Landscape Management (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Macroevolution and Paleontology (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Marine Sciences (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Marketing, Management & Food Industry Economics (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Molecular Biology (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Molecular/Cellular Plant-Microbe Interactions (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Molecular and General Genetics (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Neurobiology (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Nutritional Biochemistry (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Ornamentals and Urban Integrated Pest Management (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Plant Breeding and Genetics (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Plant Cell Biology (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Plant Environmental & Stress Physiology (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Plant Molecular Genetics & Plant Biotechnology (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Plant Physiology (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Policy Studies & Rural Education (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Plant Structure, Development & Evolution (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Plant-Arthropod Interactions (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Post Harvest Science (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Population and Community Ecology (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Population and Development Program (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Population & Ecological Genetics/Molecular Evolution (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - (Sustainable) Poultry Systems Program (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Processing Technologies for Value-Added Food Products (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Prokaryotic Biology (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Quantitative Analysis in Economics (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Risk Communication (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Resource Policy, Management & Human Dimensions (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Seed Science (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Soil and Water Resources (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - State and Local Governance (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Statistics (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Sustainability of Food and Agriculture Systems in Communities (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Systematic Biology (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Teacher Education (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Theoretical Biology (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Tropical Farming Systems (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Undergrad Communication Competencies (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Undergrad Quantitative and Technological Literacy (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Vegetable Crops Systems (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Vertebrate Biology (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Waste Management (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Weed Science (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Wetlands (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Youth Science and Citizenship Education (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Fiscal Year Summaries, ending 6/30/98 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Interest Income from Endowed Funds by Department, February 1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Follow up on Budget Conference (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Department of Animal Science (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Agriculture and Biological Engineering (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Agriculture, Resource and Managerial Economics (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, American Indian Program (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Biochemistry, Molecular and Cell Biology (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Department of Biometrics (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Center for the Environment (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Department of Communication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - CaRDI- Community and Rural Development Institiute, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Cornell Cooperative Extension (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Cornell Plantations (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Section of Ecology and Systematics (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Department of Education (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Department of Entomology (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Department of Entomology, Geneva NY (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Department of Food Science (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Food Science and Technology (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Department of Fruit and Vegetable Science (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Genetics and Development (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Horticultural Sciences (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, L.H. Bailey Hortorium (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Lab of Ornithology (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Landscape Architecture (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Mann Library (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Media and Technology Services (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Microbiology (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Natural Resources (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Neurology and Behavior (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Department of Nutritional Sciences (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Physiology (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Plant Breeding (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Plant Pathology (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Plant Pathology- Geneva, NY (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Rural Sociology (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Fiscal Year 1999-2000, Soil, Crop and Atmospheric Sciences (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Proposal for Div. of Biological Sciences (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - President's Academic Cabinet (PAC)- Biological Sciences Task Force (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - PAC- Biological Sciences Task Force (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - PAC- Biological Science Review (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - PAC- Biological Review (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Relational Database (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - NERA- Northeastern Association of State Agriculture Experiment Stations, Directors, Ad Hoc Regional Committee on Database (Box 6, Folder 46)